National Capital Parks (NCP) Photograph Collection P034
Stage
- Condemnation and Demolition of Buildings
  - C & O Canal - 7809 Riverside Avenue - Cabin John, MD, 1955 December 15 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - C & O Canal - 6410 Woodrow Avenue - Cabin John, MD, 1954 February 23 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - C & O Canal - 6412 Woodrow Avenue - Cabin John, MD, 1955 December 15 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - C & O Canal - 210 & 212 Columbia Avenue - Glen Echo, MD, 1954 April 9 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - C & O Canal - 200 Harvard Avenue - Glen Echo, MD, 1954 April 9 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - C & O Canal - Lock House, Lock 5, 1955 March 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - C & O Canal - Lock House, Lock 6, 1954 March 8 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - C & O Canal - Lock House, Lock 8, 1957 October 30 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - C & O Canal - Lock House, Lock 9, 1957 October 30 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - C & O Canal - Lock House, Lock 10, 1957 October 30 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Nevius Tract, 1953 August 25 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Parks - Fort Dupont (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Parks - Fort Reno, 1953 March 26 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Parks - Rock Creek, 1959 October 8 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Parks - Fort Stanton (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Takoma Recreation Center (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Virginia - Glebe Road, 1953 March 26 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Virginia - Mount Vernon Boulevard, 1953 August 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Erosion
  - Edmonds and 42nd Street, NW, 1944 September 4 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Fort Drive, 1944 May 8-1944 May 10 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Glover Archbold Parkway, 1944 May 8-1944 May 10 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Hillcrest Recreation Center (30th and Erie Street, SE), 1944 May 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Melvin Hazen Parkway, 1944 March 28 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Arlington Farms, 1944 May 3 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Brentwood Park, 1944 May 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Langdon Recreation Center (18th Street, NE), 1944 May 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - North and South Portal Drive, 1944 May 10-1944 September 4 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Oxon Run Parkway, 1944 May 10 00:00:00 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Piney Branch Parkway, 1942 March 12-1944 May 8 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Portland Place, SE, 1944 February (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Rock Creek Park, 1944 March 28-1944 August 24 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Shepherd Parkway, 1944 March 9-1944 August 24 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - West and East Beach Drive, 1944 May 8-1944 May 10 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Whitehaven Parkway, 1944 May 8 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Floods
  - 1936 - Anacostia Park, 1936 March 17-1936 March 19 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1936 - Dyke Construction, 1936 March 25-1936 April 10 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1936 - East Potomac Park, 1936 March 17-1936 March 19 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 1936 - Haines Point, 1936 March 17 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1936 - Mount Vernon Memorial Highway, 1936 March 19 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1936 - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway, 1936 March 16-1936 March 19 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1936 - Tidal Basin, 1936 March 17 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1936 - West Potomac Park, 1936 March 19 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1937 - East Potomac Park, 1937 April (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1936 - Anacostia Park, 1936 March 17-1936 March 19 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1936 - Dyke Construction, 1936 March 25-1936 April 10 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1936 - East Potomac Park, 1936 March 17-1936 March 19 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 1936 - Haines Point, 1936 March 17 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1936 - Mount Vernon Memorial Highway, 1936 March 19 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1936 - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway, 1936 March 16-1936 March 19 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1936 - Tidal Basin, 1936 March 17 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1936 - West Potomac Park, 1936 March 19 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1937 - East Potomac Park, 1937 April (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1936 - Anacostia Park, 1936 March 17-1936 March 19 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1936 - Dyke Construction, 1936 March 25-1936 April 10 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1936 - East Potomac Park, 1936 March 17-1936 March 19 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 1936 - Haines Point, 1936 March 17 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1936 - Mount Vernon Memorial Highway, 1936 March 19 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1936 - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway, 1936 March 16-1936 March 19 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1936 - Tidal Basin, 1936 March 17 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1936 - West Potomac Park, 1936 March 19 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1937 - East Potomac Park, 1937 April (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1937 - (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1937 - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway, 1937 April 27-1937 April 30 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 1937 - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway, 1937 April (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 1937 - West Potomac Park, 1937 April (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 1938 - Dyke Construction, 1938 January 3-1938 February 18 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 1942 - Anacostia Park, 1942 October 18 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 1942 - Arlington Memorial Bridge, 1942 October 17 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - 1942 - C & O Canal, 1942 October 17-1942 October 20 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 1940 - C & O Canal, 1940 September 10 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 1942 - East Potomac Park, 1942 October 16-1942 October 24 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 1942 - Rock Creek Park, 1942 October 16 00:00:00 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - 1942 - West Potomac Park, 1942 October 16-1942 October 17 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Fountains
  - Bartholdi Fountain, 1927 April 8-1927 April 22 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Butt-Millett Fountain, 1934 October-1940 September 10 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Chevy Chase Circle - Newlands Memorial Fountain, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Columbus Fountain, 1926 June 14-1929 July 22 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Dupont Circle, 1931 June 6-1942 July 27 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Federal Reserve Building, 1938 February 21-1940 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Franklin Park, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mellon Fountain Pump Room, 1953 December 18 00:00:00 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Neptune Fountain, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Public Fountains, 1927 August 12-1927 August 13 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Truxton Circle Fountain, 1932-1937 April 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Union Station Fountain, 1931 June 6-1934 October (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Forts
  - Fort Dupont, 1951 September 13-1954 September 23 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Fort Foote - Fire, 1945 March 26 00:00:00 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Fort Foote - NCP Personnel, Activities, 1938 June (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Fort Foote - River Bank North of Wharf, 1934 July 20 00:00:00 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Fort Foote - Views from, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Fort Hunt - Bar-B-Q, 1937 September 15 00:00:00 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Fort Hunt - Bonus Army Camp, 1933 May 13-1933 May 20 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Fort Hunt - Grounds, 1934 January 23-1938 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Fort Hunt - NCP Picnic, 1937 May 5 00:00:00 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Fort Hunt - National Press Club Outing, 1950 June 17 00:00:00 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Fort Hunt - Picnic Area, 1936 May 21-1955 July 30 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Fort Stevens, 1972 May 15 00:00:00 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Maps and Plans
  - Airport, ca. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Capitol Grounds, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Cherry Blossom Traffic Control, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Circles of Washington, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Federal Triangle, ca. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Highways and Safety Engineering, 1921-1926 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Maryland, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Meridian Hill Park (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Mount Vernon Highway Planting Plans, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Parking Survey and Zoning, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Parkways and Boulevards, 1922-1931 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Recreation, 1916-1957 June 15 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - 16th Street Concourse, 1928-1946 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Thoroughfares, 1928-1936 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Transit, 1927 December (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Washington and Environs, 1926-1930 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Waterfront Development, 1924-1930 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Zoning, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Federal Triangle, 1932 October 14 00:00:00 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Military
  - Camp Carderock, MD - Building Exteriors, 1944 December (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Camp Carderock, MD - Building Interiors, 1944 December (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Camp Carderock, MD - Riverfront, 1944 December (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Camp Carderock, MD - Woods, 1944 December (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Camp Carderock, MD - Building Exteriors, 1944 December (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Camp Carderock, MD - Woods, 1944 December (Box 20, Folder 3)
- National Capital Parks
  - Equipment - Benches, 1937 February 9-1937 March 19 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Equipment - Benches, 1934-1953 September 29 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Moved Negative
  - Equipment - Boats, 1948 April 13-1948 July 17 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Equipment - Comfort Station, 1958 July 16-1959 December 10 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Equipment - Comfort Station, 1937 August 2-1957 February 19 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Equipment - Drinking Fountains, 1945 April 28 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Equipment - Chairs, 1928 June 6-1936 November 5 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Equipment - Fireplaces/Incinerators, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Equipment - Benches, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Equipment - Benches, 1937 February 9-1937 March 19 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Equipment - Boats, 1934-1953 September 29 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Equipment - Comfort Station, 1948 April 13-1948 July 17 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Equipment - Comfort Station, 1958 July 16-1959 December 10 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Equipment - Drinking Fountains, 1937 August 2-1957 February 19 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Equipment - Chairs, 1945 April 28 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Equipment - Fireplaces/Incinerators, 1928 June 6-1936 November 5 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Equipment - Light Poles, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Equipment - Picnic Tables (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Equipment - Playground, 1959 September 29-1959 November 10 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Equipment - Posts, 1950 September 26 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Equipment - Rescue of Raymond, the Park Horse, 1933 April (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Equipment - Signs, 1936-1937 November (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Equipment - Squirrel Houses, 1937 December-1938 January (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Equipment - Trailers, 1950 September 15 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Equipment - Trash Receptacle, 1937 March 5-1954 March 3 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Air-Raid/Blackout, 1942 March 6 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Edgers, 1958 May 7-1958 November 21 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Flagpole Cleaner, 1945 November 2 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Line Painter Truck, 1937 May 6 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Mowers, 1936 August 8-1955 October 7 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Sand Spreader, 1936 November 4-1937 February 6 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Shops, 1936 June 18-1958 November 20 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Snow Plows and Blowers, 1937 February 16-1947 February 24 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Spraying Truck, 1952 October 2 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Street Flusher, 1936 October 28-1939 December 7 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Street Sweeper, 1937 February 19 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Maintenance/Equipment - Surplus, 1951 March 19-1952 May 19 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Personnel - Achievements - Joe Unger, 1944 January 28 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Personnel - Awardees, 1945 May 11 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Personnel - Awardees, 1957 February 5-1960 June (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Personnel - Chiefs, 1953 July 1-1957 December 16 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Personnel - Christmas Party, 1958 December 22 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Personnel - Colored Women Employees, 1943 April 8 00:00:00 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Personnel - Guards, 1958 December 5-1958 December 19 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Personnel - Mechanical Shops, 1937 June 12-1937 July 19 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Meetings, 1957 March 20-1958 November 24 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Mr. Sager's Office Force, 1955 September 8 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Navy Building Offices, 1937 February 4 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Personnel - Office of Public Buildings and Grounds, 1900 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Personnel - Painters, 1959 April (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Personnel - Park Police and Guard Uniforms, 1951 July 17 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Personnel - Retirements, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Personnel - Summer Park Naturalists, 1957 August 16 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Personnel - Superintendents, 1959 November 19 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Personnel - Training - Rock Creek Park Fire School, 1942 June 23 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Personnel - Uniforms/Laborers, 1937 May (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Personnel - Unknown Employee, 1952 December 18 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Personal - Wedding Shower, 1956 April 13 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Shops - Carpentry, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Equipment - Benches (Negative), 1937 February 9 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Equipment - Benches (Negative), 1937 February 9 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Equipment - Boats (Negative), 1938 May 31 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Negative Damaged
- Parks
  - Anacostia, 1947 July 31 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Banneker, 1949 May 4 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Barry Farms, 1931 September (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Folger - Construction, 1936 March 15-1936 May 1 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Folger - Plans, 1935 February-1936 January 27 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Folger - Pre-Renovation, 1934 December 3-1936 January 18 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Folger - Post-Renovation, 1936 July-1938 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Folger - Trees, 1936 May 8-1937 August 5 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Garfield, 1926 July 26-1945 July 26 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Happy Hollow, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Hillcrest, 1949 October 31 00:00:00 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Hoover, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Kelly-Miller, 1949 June 6-1963 April 3 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Kennedy - Dedication, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Lincoln, 1931 May 20-1944 November 6 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Lincoln - Tree Surgery, 1934 September-1935 December 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Palisades, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Parking, 1952 September 17 00:00:00 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Rock Creek - Access Bridge to Riding Stable, 1958 October 7-1959 April 10 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Rock Creek - Campfire Girl Plantings, 1938 April (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Rock Creek - Riding Stable, 1958 August 11-1959 January 8 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Rock Creek - 16th Street Reservoir Demolition, 1937 December 17-1938 October 4 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Takoma, 1933 May 2-1935 November 21 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Taft (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Takoma, 1936 March 13-1957 April 24 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Turkey Thicket, 1931 March 6-1934 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Turkey Thicket, 1935 February 19-1948 October 12 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Twin Oaks, 1933 December 7 00:00:00 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Zoo - Animals, 1932 January 25-1934 May (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Zoo - Buildings, 1931 August 13-1932 April 18 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Zoo - Entrances, 1928 June 9-1932 August 15 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Zoo - General Views, 1931 September-1933 February (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - East Potomac Park - Tourist Camp (Negative) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - East Potomac Park - Tourist Camp (Negative), 1931 June 20 00:00:00 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - East Potomac Park - Tourist Camp (Negative), 1931 May 20 00:00:00 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - East Potomac Park - Tourist Camp (Negative), 1931 May 20 00:00:00 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Rock Creek - Campfire Girl Plantings (Negative), 1938 June 3 00:00:00 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Turkey Thicket (Negative) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Turkey Thicket (Negative) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Turkey Thicket (Negative) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Lincoln Park (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Lincoln Park (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Strip Negative
  - Lincoln Park (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln Park (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Rock Creek - Access Bridge to Riding Stable (Negative), 1958 October 7 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Rock Creek - Access Bridge to Riding Stable (Negative), 1958 October 7 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Rock Creek - Access Bridge to Riding Stable (Negative), 1959 March 9 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Rock Creek - Access Bridge to Riding Stable (Negative), 1959 March 9 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Rock Creek - Campfire Girl Plantings (Negative), 1938 April (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Rock Creek - Riding Stable (Negative), 1958 August 11 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Rock Creek - Riding Stable (Negative), 1958 August 11 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Rock Creek - Riding Stable (Negative), 1958 August 11 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Rock Creek - Riding Stable (Negative), 1958 September 11 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Rock Creek - Riding Stable (Negative), 1958 September 11 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Rock Creek - Riding Stable (Negative), 1958 September 11 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Rock Creek - Riding Stable (Negative), 1958 October 7 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Rock Creek - Riding Stable (Negative), 1958 October 7 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Takoma (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Takoma (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Takoma (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Takoma (Negative), 1939 October 28 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Takoma (Negative), 1939 October 28 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Takoma (Negative), 1939 October 28 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Takoma (Negative), 1939 October 28 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Takoma (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Takoma (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Parkways
  - George Washington Parkway - Abongdon, 1935 June 1 00:00:00 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - George Washington Parkway - Arlington Memorial Bridge, 1938 September 13-1938 October 20 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - George Washington Parkway - Bridges, 1929 December 20-1949 April 15 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - George Washington Parkway - Culverts, 1936 October (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - George Washington Parkway - Dumps, ca. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - George Washington Parkway - Key Bridge Vicinity, 1935 July (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - George Washington Parkway - Abongdon, 1935 June 1 00:00:00 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - George Washington Parkway - Arlington Memorial Bridge, 1938 September 13-1938 October 20 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - George Washington Parkway - Bridges, 1929 December 20-1949 April 15 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - George Washington Parkway - Culverts, 1936 October (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - George Washington Parkway - Dumps, ca. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - George Washington Parkway - Key Bridge Vicinity, 1935 July (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - George Washington Parkway - Lee Boulevard Vicinity (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - George Washington Parkway - Leiter Estate, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - George Washington Parkway - Leiter Estate Fire, 1945 February 23-1945 February 24 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - George Washington Parkway - Leiter Estate Grounds, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - George Washington Parkway - Litter, 1941 March 21-1955 January 28 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - George Washington Parkway - Maryland Side, 1961 April 7 00:00:00 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - George Washington Parkway - Planting, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - George Washington Parkway - Pollution, 1944 October 2-1952 May 29 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - George Washington Parkway - Roaches Run - Aerial Views, 1934 August 1 00:00:00 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - George Washington Parkway - Roaches Run - CCC Workers, 1934 July 20-1935 July 12 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - George Washington Parkway - Roaches Run - Ducks, 1934 January-1938 November (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - George Washington Parkway - Roaches Run - Ducks, 1940 March 8-1951 November 20 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - George Washington Parkway - Roaches Run - Flooding, 1935 April 12-1937 April (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - George Washington Parkway - Roaches Run - Unlawful, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - George Washington Parkway - Roaches Run - Views (Land), 1932-1940 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - George Washington Parkway - Roaches Run - Views (Water), 1934-1944 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - George Washington Parkway - Roaches Run - Wildlife, 1935 August 18-1941 November 29 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - George Washington Parkway - Roadwork, 1931 August 24-1937 December 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - George Washington Parkway - Rosslyn Vicinity, 1951 March 28 00:00:00 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - George Washington Parkway - Stonework, 1934 October 15-1935 March 4 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - George Washington Parkway - US Route 50 Vicinity, 1959 September 8 00:00:00 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - George Washington Parkway - Winter, 1935 December-1936 February 9 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - George Washington Parkway - Worthington Oil Company Encroachment, 1944 September 7-1949 June 23 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - George Washington Parkway - Worthington Oil Company Seepage, 1950 January 11-1953 March 11 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Construction, 1934-1937 December 14 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - K Street Vicinity, 1929 June 24-1937 February 19 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - New Hampshire Avenue Vicinity, 1928 July 8-1931 August 24 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Pennsylvania Avenue Vicinity, 1922-1929 June 24 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Pilings Removal, 1957 April-1957 May (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Planting, 1930 July 11-1937 March 30 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Red Bud Trees (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Road Resurfacing, 1951 September 7 00:00:00 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Titanic Memorial Vicinity, 1930 May 21-1937 May 12 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Virginia Avenue Vicinity, 1926 November 1-1935 August 25 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Bridges - Calvert Street (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Bridges - M Street, 1927-1930 August 19 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Bridges - P Street, 1930 August 19-1939 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Bridle Path, 1931 August 24 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Francis Junior High School, 1938 February 7 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Grading, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - New Road, 1935 November-1943 January 15 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - P Street Vicinity, 1927 January 27-1943 January 15 (Box 17, Folder 5)